foreign
[Music]
we continue to enjoy a deluge of
snowfall in my Valley to the point that
many are snowed in quite consistently
I found myself spending even more time
than usual at home by the fire warming
my toes and this week was no different
however I recently went with my mother
to an antique shop as we were both
feeling a bit of Cabin Fever it was much
needed and I found some lovely items to
use in the kitchen
it's always a pleasure to explore these
places full of so many old things with
so many stories
[Music]
foreign
ly after my visit to the shop the
temperatures warmed up a bit and I got
out on my snowshoes to enjoy the forest
surrounding my home checking on the
Sleepy Pines and sending them well
wishes for an abundant spring
[Music]
thank you
foreign
[Music]
as The Long Winter stretches into the
new year it has made me reflective on my
path and the goals I used to hold on to
so tightly goals regarding what it means
to be successful
and I thought it would be interesting to
hear what you define to be success and
what things we can learn but also
unlearn as we go into this new chapter
and a new beginning
I always received a clear message of
what success is from movies commercials
and media I consumed as a child
first to be successful is to have many
many friends which wasn't something I
was ever that good at
second your job will be one of the most
important things in your life which was
something I was good at because I always
tended to get consumed with my career
goals particularly when I was much
younger
third once you achieve your dream home
job or relationship you will also
magically resolve all your personal
problems fourth be happy that you have
all these things and don't ever suggest
that you're struggling to find deep
fulfillment in them
now when stated like this it seems very
childish and rather silly to believe any
of these things actually work that way
we are too complex and Too Human to
simplify ourselves in such manner
I recently came across a book that had
the title there is no cure for being
human and while I haven't read the book
that line stuck with me because it's
true I like to think that the reason we
are live is to be stewards of the earth
to connect to give to love and learn
about ourselves and evolve into the best
version we can be
that path cannot be an easy one and
that's the whole point
[Music]
foreign
and if it was so easy to Simply fulfill
an external definition of success in
order to resolve all those internal
feelings of lack of fulfillment I would
have little drive to develop who I am my
spirituality and try to be a little
better each day
and yet these beliefs are deeply
intertwined in my experience and
particularly my mindset when I was in
university and it still follows me to
this day and as I've achieved many of my
dreams many I never thought I would I
continue to find Amusement in the fact
that none of them have ever fulfilled me
long term
presently I'm pursuing my new definition
of true success and that is a feeling
that cannot be taken away from me so
easily it is something deeper in my
heart
[Music]
so this year I'm working on unlearning a
lot of messages that often seem rather
materialistic or superficial at their
core
perhaps we can unlearn things together
and make our own path to Joy and success
in a less conventional way
[Music]
I always find myself painting flowers
this time of year I think it is simply
because
the forest the nature everywhere around
me just feels so lacking in life even
though that's not necessarily true it's
just dormant but usually around
mid-January I really start to miss the
Spring it has been a wild winter I think
cumulatively we've probably gotten close
to five and a half maybe even six feet
of snow in some places and it's
hard to believe but it's also wonderful
because we are a little tourist town and
so we really rely on a good ski season
during the holidays so we are all kind
of celebrating but also wishing we could
um not have to shovel our driveways for
the 16th time this month my little cat
loves to just put her paws all into my
watercolors and then walk around the
house she's done it multiple times
oh my goodness by the way I've totally
forgot to say this but thank you so much
for the support of my Etsy Shop it has
been so exciting to reopen and I have
seen that my Owl print and my rabbit
print have been quite popular and I
really appreciate it those are some of
my favorite paintings and I'm so glad
you enjoy them too so thank you I can
remember when I got my very first job
um I worked at a library a little bit
when I was a teenager and I remember I
felt so insanely proud of myself for
getting a job I think I was the only one
who interviewed for it but you know I
don't think high schoolers were just
lining up to work at a library but I was
I was but I remember I felt so proud of
myself and I felt so kind of uh
successful in my own small way and I
felt that same way after I graduated
University and started working at a
bookstore and I finally was able to
afford an apartment governments and I
just felt so full and so excited and
just very full of that feeling of look
look Mom I'm doing it you know it was a
really exciting feeling even though you
know it was not always easy I think
always those kind of two things have
always been the only things that really
contribute to my feelings of success of
course being able to have some sort of
living Arrangement and a job I think
after that after those things are found
in which you can you know live
um
kind of that feeling of success is um
kind of diminishing returns I think and
you get to a point where you realize
that you need to um
seek out something much deeper in order
to feel that more long-term fulfillment
however this new year I really want to
work on kind of unlearning a lot of
messages that I really took to heart
when I was much younger and I realize
they're a little still with me perhaps
success for you will be very
unconventional maybe it will not be you
know what your family said it should be
or your Society or even just what you
told yourself it could be spending a day
snowed in talking to your cat which is
what I'm doing right now
right mavi
so success can be very unconventional
here's my example oh Lord it was just
something I was thinking a lot about
coming into the new year and things I
want to work on in regards to my life
and hopefully gain some wisdom from all
of you you know all together I'm sure we
can offer some really interesting
insights
into our own Journeys and at least offer
some different examples of what success
is to you I had an absolutely wonderful
time going to antique shops I just
always love it it just feels like a
little treasure hunt one thing that I
did find was this extremely heavy
picture frame and it has a woman on it
and I don't know who she is or what her
story is
but
I really liked her expression and she
seemed so thoughtful and um happy and so
I picked it up I think it was like four
dollars so I may end up removing the
photo and putting it in a very honored
place and replacing it with a wedding
photo or something like that but I
really liked it so
that's one of my favorite things about
antique shops too seeing old photos of
people that you don't know that probably
lived very interesting lives that you
will never know the details of and yet
you see the essence perhaps of who they
were in a photograph in a little shop in
a Dusty corner and everyone's Legacy
kind of lives on in little ways I've
been painting for a while now and my
puppy Iker is very excited to get
outdoors and play in the snow and
because thankfully it is no longer
negative 30 degrees
um we're gonna go out for a walk and
probably take the snowshoes out again I
think we're going to head out in just a
little bit and see what Adventures we
get up to I hope you have a wonderful
week do share your thoughts and dreams
for the new year down below
and I will see you all soon